<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Karan Shah</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Karan Shah</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog Post </title>
      <link>/blog/blog-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/blog-post/</guid>
      <description>I really enjoyed learning how to use Python this semester in class. Having a background in java and R I really wanted to be exposed to Python as I have heard that it is very popular withing the computer science community.
The following are examples of how i learned to use Python in class:
list1= [1,2,3,4] list1[2] ## 3 list1[0] ## 1 list1[1:] ## [2, 3, 4] Using python we can have a vector and look through it and select certain positions that we want.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects Here are some projects I have been working on:
  Project 1
  Project 2
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploratory Data Project</title>
      <link>/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project1/</guid>
      <description>Ny first data set is about the crime rates in the different states of India. This data set was interesting for me as my family is from India and I regulary go back and visit. It was interesting to see the different crime rates split up by different cirime types in different states of India. In order to analyze this data further I wanted to compare this data to that of another city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2</title>
      <link>/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project2/</guid>
      <description>Karan Shah kjs3349
The MedGPA dataset contains variables that are important predictors of getting accepted into medical school. This dataset lists the statistics of students who recieved admission into Medical school and those who got denied from Medical School. The dataset contains the following variables: Acceptance to Medical Schoo as a binomial variable, Sex, BCPM, GPA, VR, PS, WS, BS, MCAT Scores, and the number of applications the specific student submitted.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>